Jon: We're here to say goodbye
to our brothers and sisters.
乔恩：我们是来告别的
致我们的兄弟姐妹。
To our fathers and mothers.
献给我们的父亲和母亲。
To our friends.
敬我们的朋友。
Our fellow men and women
who set aside their differences...
我们的男女同胞
他们抛开了分歧……
To fight together...
一起战斗……
And die together
一起死去
so that others might live.
好让别人活下去。
Everyone in this world
这个世界上的每个人
owes them a debt
that can never be repaid.
欠他们一个人情
那是永远无法偿还的。
It is our duty and our honor
这是我们的责任，也是我们的荣誉
to keep them alive in memory...
让他们活在记忆中……
For those who come after us
为那些在我们之后的人
and those who come after them,
那些在他们之后的人，
for as long as men draw breath.
只要人类还活着。
They were the shields
that guarded the realms of men.
他们是盾牌
守护着人类的王国。
And we shall never see
their like again.
我们永远也看不到
他们又来了。
Have you seen Arya?
你看到艾莉亚了吗？
You can still smell
the burning bodies,
你还能闻到
燃烧的尸体，
and that's where your head is at?
这就是你的想法吗？
- I just want to thank her for...
- I'm sure you do.
-我只是想谢谢她…
-我相信你知道。
- Look, it's not about that.
- Of course it's about that, you twat.
-听着，这不是问题。
-当然了，你个笨蛋。
Why shouldn't it be?
为什么不应该呢？
The dead are dead. You're not.
死人就是死人。你不是。
Daenerys: Gendry.
Daenerys: Gendry。
That's right, isn't it?
没错，不是吗？
Yes, your grace.
是的，陛下。
You're Robert Baratheon's son.
你是劳勃·拜拉席恩的儿子。
You are aware
he took my family's throne
你知道吗？
他夺走了我家族的王位
and tried to have me murdered?
还想杀了我？
I didn't even know he was my father
until after he was dead.
我都不知道他是我父亲
直到他死后。
Yes, he's dead.
是的，他死了。
His brothers are, too.
他的兄弟们也是。
So who's lord of storm's end now?
现在谁是风息堡的领主？
I don't know, your grace.
我不知道，陛下。
Does anyone?
有人吗?
I think you should be
lord of storm's end.
我觉得你应该
风息堡领主。
I can't be. I'm a bastard.
我不可能。我是个私生子。
No, you are lord gendry Baratheon
of storm's end,
不，你是詹德利·拜拉席恩大人
暴风雨的结束，
the lawful son of Robert Baratheon.
劳勃·拜拉席恩的合法儿子
Because that is what I have made you.
因为这就是我创造的你。
To lord gendry Baratheon
of storm's end.
敬詹德利·拜拉席恩大人
暴风雨的结束。
To gendry!
gendry !
People: Lord gendry!
人们：詹德利勋爵！
Man: Gendry!
男:Gendry !
Man 2: Gendry! Man 3: Gendry!
男2：詹德利！男3：詹德利！
Man 4: Lord gendry!
男4：詹德利勋爵！
Man 5: Gendry!
男5：詹德利！
Man 6: That's easy, isn't it?
男6：这很简单，不是吗？
- A fitting reward for a hero.
- Samwell: Uh, hold on.
-这是对英雄的奖励。
等一下。
Tyrion: And a lord of storm's end
who will be forever onal to you.
提利昂：也是风暴尽头的领主
谁会永远爱你。
- Come, my lord.
- See?
-来吧，大人。
——看到了吗?
You're not the only one who's clever.
你不是唯一一个聪明的人。
Woman: I have to go down
and get another barrel.
女：我得下去了
再来一桶。
Jaime: We fought dead things
and lived to talk about it.
詹姆：我们和死人搏斗
还能活着谈论这件事。
If this isn't the time to drink,
when is?
如果现在不是喝酒的时候，
是什么时候?
The last time I saw her, I told her
I'd kill her if I ever saw her again.
我最后一次见到她时，我告诉了她
再让我见到她，我就杀了她。
- I'm sure you had your reasons.
- I did.
-我相信你有你的理由。
-是的。
- I do.
- So did you?
-是的。
-你也是吗？
Never got the chance.
从来没有机会。
She did it to herself.
是她自己弄的。
Or her god did it to her.
或者是她的神对她做的。
The lord of light.
光之王。
We play his game for him,
we fight his war and win,
我们替他玩他的游戏
我们为他的战争而战并取得胜利
and then
然后
he fucks off.
他走开了。
No signs, no blessings.
Who knows what he wants?
没有预兆，就没有祝福。
谁知道他想要什么？
I don't imagine
thinking about that subject
我不能想象
思考这个问题
will leave you
any happier than before.
会离开你
比以前更快乐了。
And what if
I'm not trying to be happy?
如果
我不是想要开心吗？
Then you're in luck.
那你就走运了。
We may have defeated them,
我们也许打败了他们
but we still have us to contend with.
但我们仍有自己的对手。
Thank you. I feel much better.
谢谢你！我感觉好多了。
Man: More ale!
男：再来点麦芽酒！
This is clever.
这很聪明。
Even better than the saddle
I designed for you.
甚至比马鞍还好
我是为你设计的。
It's the same as the one
daeron Targaryen built
和那个是一样的
丹伦·坦格利安建造的
for his crippled nephew 120 years ago.
为他残疾的侄子准备的。
I liked that one.
我喜欢那个。
Tyrion: You know our history
better than anyone.
提利昂：你知道我们的历史
比任何人都好。
That will be useful
as lord of winterfell.
这很有用
作为临冬城主。
I'm not lord of winterfell.
我不是临冬城主。
You're the only surviving
trueborn son of ned stark.
你是唯一的幸存者
奈德·史塔克的亲生儿子。
You don't want it.
你不会想要的。
I don't really want anymore.
我真的不想要了。
I envy you.
我真羡慕你。
You shouldn't envy me.
你不应该嫉妒我。
Mostly I live in the past.
大部分时间我都活在过去。
Tormund: All of it. Man: Go on.
托蒙德：所有的。男：继续。
- No, not in one go.
- Go on. I believe in you.
-不，不是一次。
-继续。我相信你。
Tormund: We have to
celebrate our victory.
托蒙德：我们必须这么做
庆祝我们的胜利。
Vomiting is not celebrating.
呕吐不是庆祝。
Yes, it is.
是的，它是。
Ah!
啊!
To the dragon queen!
敬龙皇后！
To Arya stark, the hero of winterfell!
敬临冬城的英雄艾莉亚·史塔克！
Woman: Drink!
女:喝!
Tormund: I'm fine!
托蒙：我很好！
Your turn.
轮到你。
- You are an only child.
- Oh.
-你是独生子。
——哦。
- I told you I was.
- You didn't.
-我告诉过你我是。
-你没有。
- I did.
- I surmised it.
-是的。
-我猜的。
Mm-hm. Drink.
嗯嗯。饮料。
Go again.
又来了。
Why does he get to go again?
为什么他能再去一次？
Because it's my game.
因为这是我的游戏。
You have danced with renly Baratheon.
你跟蓝礼·拜拉席恩跳过舞。
- Uh...
- Tyrion: Drink.
——嗯…
喝吧。
Man: The other way around!
男：反过来！
I saw him riding that thing.
我看见他骑那东西。
- We all did.
- No. No.
-我们都是。
——没有。否。
I saw him riding that thing.
我看见他骑那东西。
- That's right, you did.
- I did.
-没错，你说了。
-是的。
That's why we all agreed
to follow him.
所以我们都同意了
跟着他。
That's the kind of man he is.
他就是这样的人。
He's little...
他的小…
But he's strong.
但他很强壮。
Strong enough to befriend an enemy
强大到可以成为敌人的朋友
and get murdered for it!
并因此被谋杀！
Most people get bloody murdered,
they stay that way.
大多数人都被谋杀了
他们保持这种状态。
Not this one.
不是这个。
Yeah, I didn't have much say in that.
是啊，我没说什么。
He comes back and keeps fighting.
他回来了，继续战斗。
Here, north of the wall,
and then back here again.
这里，长城以北，
然后再回到这里。
He keeps fighting. He keeps fighting.
他一直在战斗。他一直在战斗。
He climbed on a fucking dragon
and fought.
他爬上了一条该死的龙
和战斗。
What kind of person
climbs on a fucking dragon?
什么样的人
爬上该死的龙？
A madman or a king!
一个疯子或者一个国王！
- Tyrion: Drink.
- Drink.
喝吧。
——喝。
Drink.
饮料。
Brienne: Wrong!
一起:错了!
Wrong, wrong, wrong! Drink!
错，错，错！喝!
Tyrion: Mmm!
泰瑞欧:嗯!
You were married. Before sansa.
你结婚了。珊莎。
Drink.
饮料。
You're drinking wine,
but you prefer ale!
你在喝酒，
但你更喜欢淡啤酒！
No!
不!
You're a virgin.
你还是处男。
That's a statement about the present.
这是一个关于现在的陈述。
At no point in the past,
up until this very moment,
在过去的任何时候，
直到此刻，
have you slept with a man.
你和男人睡过吗？
Or a woman.
或者一个女人。
I have to piss.
我要尿尿。
We did it! We faced those icy fucks.
我们成功了！我们面对那些冰冷的家伙。
Looked right into their blue eyes,
and here we are.
直视他们的蓝眼睛，
现在我们到了。
Now, which one of you cowards
shit in my pants?
现在，你们哪个胆小鬼
裤子里有屎？
Please pardon me for a moment.
请原谅我稍等一下。
Man: Drink it!
男：喝了它！
And after all that,
在那之后，
this fucker comes north
and takes her from me.
这混蛋往北走
把她从我身边夺走。
Just takes her, like that.
就这样带走了她。
I mean it, clegane.
我是认真的，克里格。
My heart is broken.
我心碎了。
Don't touch me.
别碰我。
Willa: You can touch me.
威拉：你可以摸我。
I'm not afraid of wildlings.
我不怕野人。
Maybe you should be.
也许你应该这么做。
Well, clegane...
嗯,clegane……
It's time to drown our sorrows.
是时候把悲伤淹没了。
I'm not done with my drink.
我还没喝完呢。
Man 1: You saved the day.
男1：你拯救了世界。
Man 2: You owe me one.
男人2：你欠我个人情。
- Don't forget that.
- Man 1: For the rest of my days.
-别忘了这点。
-男人1：在我的余生里。
Are you ready now?
你现在准备好了吗？
This is my drink.
这是我的饮料。
Sansa: She could have made you happy,
for a little while.
珊莎：她本可以让你幸福，
一段时间。
There's only one thing
that'll make me happy.
只有一件事
那样我就高兴了。
- And what's that?
- That's my fucking business.
-那是什么？
-那是我的事。
Used to be you couldn't look at me.
以前是你不敢看我。
That was a long time ago.
那是很久以前的事了。
I've seen much worse than you
since then.
我见过比你更糟糕的
从那时起。
Yes, I've heard.
是的，我听说了。
Heard you were broken in.
听说有人破门而入。
Heard you were broken in rough.
听说你伤得很重。
And he got what he deserved.
I gave it to him.
他罪有应得。
我给了他。
How?
如何?
Hounds.
猎犬。
You've changed, little bird.
你变了，小鸟。
None of it would have happened
if you'd left king's landing with me.
这一切都不会发生
如果你和我一起离开君临。
No littlefinger, no ramsay...
没有小指头，没有拉姆齐……
None of it.
都没有。
Without littlefinger,
and ramsay and the rest,
没有littlefinger,
还有拉姆齐和其他人，
I would have stayed
a little bird all my life.
我会留下来
我一辈子都是一只小鸟。
Man 1: Hey!
Man 2: Pour another one.
男1：嘿！
男2：再倒一杯。
Man 3: Hey!
男3：嘿！
Don't shoot.
不要开枪。
It's nighttime, it's freezing,
and everyone's celebrating.
现在是晚上，很冷，
每个人都在庆祝。
You should be celebrating with them.
你应该和他们一起庆祝。
I am celebrating.
我在庆祝。
Yeah, I am, too.
是的，我也是。
I'm not gendry rivers anymore.
我不再是詹德里·里弗斯了。
I'm gendry Baratheon,
lord of storm's end.
我是詹德利·拜拉席恩
风息堡领主。
By order of the queen.
这是女王的命令。
Congratulations.
祝贺你。
I don't know how to be
lord of anything.
我不知道该怎么做
主宰一切。
I hardly know how to use a fork.
我几乎不知道怎么用叉子。
All I know is that you're beautiful,
and I love you,
我只知道你很美，
我爱你
and none of it will be worth anything
if you're not with me.
这一切都将一文不值
如果你不和我在一起。
So be with me.
所以和我在一起吧。
Be my wife.
Be the lady of storm's end.
做我的妻子。
做风暴尽头的淑女。
You'll be a wonderful lord,
你会是个很棒的领主
and any lady
would be lucky to have you.
任何一位女士
有你在真是太幸运了。
But I'm not a lady.
但我不是淑女。
I never have been.
我从来没有去过。
That's not me.
那不是我。
You didn't drink.
你没有喝酒。
- I didn't drink?
- In the game.
-我没喝酒？
-在游戏中。
- I drank.
- In the game. This is dornish.
-我喝酒了。
-在游戏中。这是学院式的。
This is not the game.
This is only drinking.
这不是游戏。
这只是喝酒而已。
Suit yourself.
随便你。
Well, you keep it warm enough in here.
好吧，你在这里保持足够的温暖。
It's the first thing I learnt
when I came to the north.
这是我学到的第一件事
当我来到北方
Keep your fire going.
让你的火继续燃烧。
Every time you leave the room,
put more wood on.
每次你离开房间
再加些木头。
Well, that's very diligent.
Very responsible.
嗯，那很勤奋。
非常负责任的。
- Piss off.
- You know the first thing
-滚开。
-你知道第一件事
I learned in the north?
我在北方学到的？
I hate the fucking north.
我讨厌他妈的北方。
It grows on you.
你会喜欢它的。
I don't want things growing on me.
我不想让东西长在我身上。
How about tormund giantsbane?
托蒙德巨人贝恩怎么样？
Has he grown on you?
你越来越喜欢他了吗？
He was very sad when you left.
你走的时候他很伤心。
You sound quite jealous.
你听起来很嫉妒。
I do, dontl?
我知道，不是吗？
It's bloody hot in here.
这里太热了。
Oh, move aside.
哦，靠边站。
What are you doing?
你在干什么？
I'm taking your shirt off.
我要把你的衬衫脱了。
I've never slept with a knight before.
我从没跟骑士上过床。
I've never slept with anyone before.
我以前从没跟人睡过。
Then you have to drink.
Those are the rules.
然后你就得喝酒。
这是规则。
I told you...
我告诉过你……
Are you drunk?
你喝醉了吗？
Only a little.
只会一点点。
I didn't know ser jorah well...
我不太了解乔拉爵士……
But I know this.
但我知道。
If he could have chosen a way to die,
it would have been protecting you.
如果他可以选择一种死法，
那是在保护你。
He loved me.
他爱我。
And I couldn't love him back.
而我却无法爱他。
Not the way he wanted.
不是他想要的方式。
Not the way I love you.
不是我爱你的方式。
Is that all right?
这样可以吗？
I wish you'd never told me.
我真希望你没告诉我。
If I didn't know,
I'd be happy right now.
如果我不知道，
我现在就很高兴。
I try to forget.
我试着忘记。
Tonight I did for a while,
今晚我做了一会儿，
and then I saw them
gathered around you.
然后我看到了他们
聚集在你身边。
I saw the way they looked at you.
我看到他们看你的眼神了。
I know that look.
我知道你的表情。
So many people have looked at me
that way, but never here.
很多人都看过我
那样做，但在这里不行。
Never on this side of the sea.
从来没有在海的这一边。
I told you I don't want it.
我告诉过你我不想要。
It doesn't matter what you want.
你想要什么并不重要。
You didn't want to be
king in the north.
你不想成为
北境之王。
What happens when they demand
you press your claim,
当他们提出要求时会发生什么
你坚持你的要求
and take what is mine?
拿走属于我的东西？
I'll refuse.
我会拒绝。
You are my queen.
I don't know what else I can say.
你是我的女王。
我不知道还能说什么。
You can say nothing.
你什么也不能说。
To anyone, ever.
给任何人，永远。
Never tell them who you really are.
永远不要告诉他们你的真实身份。
Swear your brother
and samwell tarly to secrecy,
发誓你的兄弟
山姆威尔早早地去保密，
and tell no one else.
别告诉别人。
Or it will take on a life of its own
and you won't be able to control it
否则它就会自生自灭
你将无法控制它
or what it does to people.
或者它对人的影响。
No matter how many times
you bend the knee,
无论多少次
你屈膝，
no matter what you swear.
无论你发誓什么。
I want it to be the way it was
between us.
我希望一切都能回到从前
我们之间。
I have to tell sansa and Arya.
我得告诉珊莎和艾莉亚。
Sansa will want to see me gone
and you on the iron throne.
珊莎会希望我离开
而你坐在铁王座上。
She won't.
她不会。
She's not the girl you grew up with.
她不是和你一起长大的女孩了。
Not after what she's seen,
在她看到这些之后
not after what they've done to her.
在他们对她做了那些事之后。
I owe them the truth.
我欠他们真相。
Even if the truth destroys us?
即使真相毁灭了我们？
- It won't.
- It will.
-不会的。
-会的。
I've never begged for anything...
我从来没有乞求过什么……
But I'm begging you.
但我求你了。
Don't do this. Please.
不要这样做。请。
You are my queen.
你是我的女王。
Nothing will change that.
没有什么能改变这一点。
And they are my family.
他们是我的家人。
We can live together.
我们可以住在一起。
We can.
我们可以。
I've just told you how.
我已经告诉你怎么做了。
Half are gone.
一半都不见了。
The northmen as well.
还有北方人。
And the golden company
has arrived in king's landing,
还有黄金公司
已抵达君临
courtesy of the greyjoy eret.
这是葛雷乔伊家的鸟。
The balance has grown
distressingly even.
平衡在增长
甚至得吓人。
When the people find out
what we have done for them,
当人们发现时
我们为他们所做的一切
that we saved them...
我们救了他们……
Cersei will make sure
they don't believe it.
瑟曦会确保的
他们不相信。
We will hit her hard.
我们会狠狠地揍她。
We will rip her out root and stem.
我们要把她连根拔起。
The objective here is to remove Cersei
我们的目标是除掉瑟曦
without destroying king's landing.
不破坏君临城。
Varys: Thankfully,
she is losing allies by the day.
不同:谢天谢地,
她每天都在失去盟友。
Yara greyjoy has retaken
the iron islands in her queen's name.
亚拉·葛雷乔伊夺回了
她女王名下的铁群岛。
The new prince of dorne
pledges his support.
多恩的新王子
承诺支持。
No matter how many lords
turn against her,
不管有多少领主
背叛她，
as long as she sits
on the iron throne,
只要她坐着
在铁王座上
she can call herself
queen of the seven kingdoms.
她可以叫自己
七大王国的女王。
We need the capital.
我们需要资金。
I watched the people
of king's landing
我看着人们
君临城
rebel against their king
when they were hungry,
反抗他们的国王
当他们饿的时候，
and that was before winter began.
那是在冬天开始之前。
Give them the opportunity
and they will cast Cersei aside.
给他们机会
他们会抛弃瑟曦
Jon: We'll surround the city.
乔恩：我们将包围这座城市。
If the iron fleet
tries to ferry in more food,
如果铁舰队
试图运送更多的食物，
the dragons will destroy them.
龙会毁灭他们。
If the lannisters
and the golden company attack,
如果兰尼斯特家
和黄金公司的进攻，
we'll defeat them in the field.
我们会在战场上打败他们。
Once the people see
that Cersei is our only enemy,
一旦人们看到
瑟曦是我们唯一的敌人
her reign is over.
她的统治结束了。
All right.
好吧。
Sansa: The men we have left
are exhausted.
珊莎：我们剩下的人
是筋疲力尽了。
Many of them are wounded.
他们中的许多人受伤了。
They'll fight better if they have
time to rest and recuperate.
如果有，他们会打得更好
是时候休息和恢复了。
How long do you suggest?
你建议多长时间？
I can't say for certain,
not without talking to the officers.
我不能肯定，
除非和警官们谈过。
I came north to fight alongside you
我北上与你并肩作战
at great cost to my armies and myself.
我和我的军队都付出了巨大的代价。
Now that the time has come
to reciprocate, you want to postpone.
现在是时候了
作为回报，你想推迟。
It's not just our people. It's yours.
不仅仅是我们的人民。这是你的。
You want to throw them into a war
they're not ready to fight?
你想让他们卷入战争
他们还没准备好战斗吗？
The longer I leave my enemies alone,
the stronger they become.
我离开我的敌人越久，
他们变得越强大。
The northern forces
will honor their promises
北方军队
会兑现他们的承诺
and their allegiance
to the queen of the seven kingdoms.
他们的忠诚
敬七国之女王。
What you command, we will obey.
你的命令，我们都服从。
Tyrion: So...
泰瑞欧:所以…
If all are in agreement...
如果大家都同意……
Jon and ser davos
will ride down the kingsroad
琼恩和戴佛斯爵士
会骑上国王大道吗
with the northern troops
和北方军队一起
and the bulk of the remaining
Dothraki and unsullied.
剩下的大部分
多斯拉克人，无垢者。
A smaller group of us
will ride to white harbor,
我们中的一小部分人
将骑到白色的港湾，
and sail from there to dragonstone
然后从那里坐船去龙石岛
with our queen and her dragons
accompanying us from above.
我们的女王和她的龙
从上面陪伴我们。
Ser Jaime has chosen to remain here,
as a guest of the lady of winterfell.
詹姆爵士选择留在这里，
作为临冬城夫人的客人。
We have won the great war.
我们赢得了这场大战。
Now we will win the last war.
现在我们将赢得最后一场战争。
In all seven kingdoms,
在这七个王国里，
men will live without fear and cruelty
人们将在没有恐惧和残忍的情况下生活
under their rightful queen.
在他们合法的女王之下。
We need a word.
我们需要一个词。
You understand we'd all be dead
if not for her.
你知道我们都会死的
如果不是为了她。
We'd be corpses
marching down to king's landing.
我们会变成尸体
向君临进发。
Arya's the one
that killed the night king.
艾莉亚才是那个
杀死了夜王。
Her men gave their lives
defending winterfell...
她的手下献出了生命
捍卫winterfell……
And we will never forget them.
我们永远不会忘记他们。
That doesn't mean
that I want to knee! To someone who...
这并不意味着
我要跪下来！给那些……
I swore myself and the north
to her cause.
我发誓我自己和北境
为了她的事业。
I respect that.
我尊重这一点。
You respect it?
你尊重它？
We needed her.
我们需要她。
We needed her army, her dragons.
我们需要她的军队，她的龙。
You did the right thing.
你做得对。
And we're doing the right thing
telling you
我们在做正确的事
告诉你
we don't trust your queen.
我们不相信你的女王。
- You don't know her yet.
- I'll never know her.
-你还不了解她。
-我永远不会认识她。
She's not one of us.
她不是我们中的一员。
If you only trust the people
you grew up with,
只要你相信人民
你是和，
you won't make many allies.
你不会有很多盟友。
That's all right.
没关系。
I don't need many allies.
我不需要很多盟友。
- Jon: Arya...
- We're family.
艾莉亚……
-我们是一家人。
The four of us.
我们四个。
The last of the starks.
史塔克家族的最后一个人。
I've never been a stark.
我从来都不是史塔克家族的人。
Sansa: You are.
珊莎：你是。
You're just as much ned stark's child
as any of us.
你也是奈德·史塔克的孩子
和我们所有人一样。
You're my brother.
你是我的兄弟。
Not my half-brother
or my bastard brother.
不是我同父异母的兄弟
或者我的私生子弟弟。
My brother.
我的兄弟。
It's your choice.
这是你的选择。
I need to tell you something.
我要告诉你一件事。
But you have to swear
you'll never tell another soul.
但你必须发誓
你不会告诉别人的。
What is it?
这是什么？
You have to swear it,
before I tell you.
你必须发誓
在我告诉你之前。
How can I promise to keep a secret
if I don't even know what it is?
我怎能保证保守秘密
如果我都不知道那是什么
Because we're family.
因为我们是一家人。
Swear it.
发誓。
I swear it.
我发誓。
Tell them.
告诉他们。
So she's going to stay here with you?
所以她要和你住在一起吗？
She's sworn to protect
the stark girls, so...
她发过誓要保护
史塔克家的女孩，所以…
Say something snide.
说些冷嘲热讽的话。
I'm happy.
我很高兴。
I'm happy that you're happy.
你开心我就开心。
I'm happy that you'll finally
have to climb for it.
我很高兴你终于
必须爬上去。
Do you know how long I've waited
to tell tall-person jokes?
你知道我等了多久吗
讲高个子的笑话？
To climbing mountains.
去爬山。
- What's she like down there?
- What?
-她在下面怎么样？
——什么?
That's not your concern.
这不关你的事。
I haven't been with a woman for years.
我好几年没跟女人在一起了。
- Give me a morsel.
- You're a dog.
-给我一点。
-你是只狗。
I am the imp, and I demand to know.
我是小恶魔，我要知道。
Bronn: I knew you were fucking her.
波隆：我就知道你在操她。
A pair of tall, blond toffs.
一对金发高个的纨绔子弟。
Must be like looking in the mirror.
肯定就像照镜子一样。
Tyrion: Ser bronn of the Blackwater.
提利昂：黑水河的波隆爵士。
Where's your drink?
你的饮料呢？
What are you...
What are you doing up north?
你在…
你在北方做什么？
What are you doing with that?
你拿着那个干什么？
Oh, this?
哦,这个吗?
This is for you.
这是给你的。
For both of you.
为了你们俩。
Tyrion: You're supposed to be south.
提利昂：你应该在南方。
You boys are a pair
of gold-plated cunts.
你们是一对
镀金的硬币。
- Do you know that?
- That's a bit rude.
-你知道吗？
-这有点不礼貌。
Year after year,
I've shoveled Lannister shit,
年复一年，
我铲过兰尼斯特家的屎
and what do I have to show?
我要展示什么呢？
You're a knight, thanks to me.
多亏了我，你成了骑士。
Thanks to me.
And that title's worth as much
多亏了我。
这个头衔也值这么多钱
as a blond hair
from your brother's ballsack.
就像一头金发
从你哥哥的蛋蛋里。
Power resides where men believe...
权力存在于人们相信的地方……
Bronn: Shut your mouth.
波隆：闭嘴。
- Tyrion: I'm just trying...
- I've never hit a dwarf before,
我只是想…
-我从来没打过侏儒
but say another word
and I will belt you.
但是再说一句话
我就用皮带抽你。
See, I don't believe you'd do that.
我不相信你会这么做。
You couldn't do it on your best day,
you one-handed fuck.
你在状态最好的时候也做不到，
你这个单手混蛋。
And your best days are long gone.
你最好的日子早已过去了。
You broke my nose!
你打断了我的鼻子！
- Bronn: I did not break your nose.
- How do you know?
我没有打断你的鼻子。
-你怎么知道？
Because I've been breaking noses
since I was your size,
因为我一直在打人鼻子
因为我和你一样大
and I know what it sounds like.
Now listen.
我知道这听起来像什么
现在听。
Your sister offered me riverrun.
你姐姐让我来奔流城
Nice big castle, good lands,
漂亮的大城堡，美丽的土地，
plenty of peasants
who do what they're told.
大量的农民
他们都是听话的人。
And you trust Cersei...
而你相信瑟曦……
I knew your sister was dead
the second I saw those dragons.
我知道你妹妹死了
我看到那些龙的那一刻
Now, your army may be torn to shit,
现在，你的军队可能被撕成碎片，
but I'd still bet
on your dragon queen to win.
但我还是敢打赌
赌你的龙皇后赢。
And it just so happens
I'm a betting man.
事情就这样发生了
我是个赌徒。
If Cersei's dead, she can't pay up.
如果瑟曦死了，她就付不起钱了。
And that's good.
Of course, the odds change
这很好。
当然，可能性在变
if the dragon queen's hand
turns up dead.
如果龙皇后的手
结果死了。
Maybe a few of her top generals
get picked off one by one.
也许是她的几个高级将领
被一个接一个地干掉。
- All of a sudden...
- Tyrion: May I speak?
-突然之间…
我可以说话吗？
Why not? Only death will shut you up.
为什么不呢?只有死亡才能让你闭嘴。
We made a deal long ago.
Do you remember?
我们很久以前就说好了。
你还记得吗？
If anyone offered me money
to kill you, you'd pay me double.
如果有人给我钱
要杀你，你会付我双倍的钱。
What's double riverrun?
双奔流城是什么？
Highgarden.
Highgarden。
You could be lord of the reach.
你可以成为河湾领主。
- Highgarden? Are you mad?
- It's better than being dead.
——Highgarden ?你疯了吗？
-总比死了好。
He's not going to kill us.
He wouldn't be talking to us if...
他不会杀我们的。
他不会跟我们说话的，如果…
The way I see it,
在我看来，
I only need
one of the Lannister brothers alive.
我只需要
兰尼斯特兄弟中活着的一个
Highgarden will never belong
to a cutthroat.
高庭永远不属于这里
对一个残忍的人。
Bronn: No? Who were your ancestors,
Bronn:没有?谁是你的祖先，
the ones who made your family rich?
那些让你们家致富的人？
Fancy lads in silk?
喜欢穿丝绸的小伙子吗？
They were fucking cutthroats.
他们是该死的杀手。
That's how all the great houses
started, isn't it?
所有的大房子都是这样的
开始了，不是吗？
With a hard bastard
who was good at killing people.
和一个冷酷的混蛋
他擅长杀人。
Kill a few hundred people,
they make you a lord.
杀死几百人
他们让你成为贵族。
Kill a few thousand,
they make you king.
杀死几千人，
他们让你成为国王。
And then all your cocksucking
grandsons can ruin the family
然后是你的口交
孙子会毁了这个家
with their cocksucking ways.
用他们舔鸡巴的方式。
Highgarden.
Highgarden。
Give me your word.
答应我。
You have my word.
我向你保证。
None of this means a thing
until we take king's landing.
这一切都毫无意义
直到我们拿下君临
We ride south in the morning.
我们早上骑马向南走。
We could use an officer with
knowledge of the city's defenses.
我们需要一位警官
对城市防御的了解。
Oh, no.
哦,不。
No, my fighting days are done.
不，我的战斗生涯结束了。
But I still got a few
killing days left, you hear me?
但我还是有一些
剩下的日子，你听到了吗？
I'll come find you
when the war is done.
我会去找你的
战争结束后。
Till then, don't die.
在那之前，不要死。
For fuck's sake.
看在上帝的份上。
On your own?
一个人？
Hound: Not anymore.
猎犬：不再是了。
I don't like crowds.
我不喜欢人群。
Arya: Me neither.
艾莉亚：我也是。
Why not? They all love you now.
为什么不呢?他们现在都爱你。
You're the big hero.
你是大英雄。
Don't like heroes.
不喜欢英雄。
It must have felt good sticking
a knife in that horned fucker.
坚持下去的感觉一定很好
把刀插在那个长角的混蛋身上。
Felt better than dying.
感觉比死好。
You're heading to king's landing?
你要去君临？
I have some unfinished business.
我还有一些未完成的事情。
Me too.
我也是。
I don't plan on coming back.
我不打算回来了。
Neither do I.
我也不知道。
Gonna leave me to die again
if I get hurt?
让我再死一次
如果我受伤了？
Probably.
可能。
My lady.
我的夫人。
"My lord" is the standard response.
“大人”是标准的回答。
Why her?
为什么她的吗?
Tyrion: You know
she loves your brother.
提利昂：你知道
她爱你哥哥。
That doesn't mean
she'll be a good queen.
这并不意味着
她会是个好王后。
You seem determined to dislike her.
你似乎下定决心不喜欢她。
A good relationship
between the iron throne and the north
良好的关系
在铁王座和北境之间
has been the core of every peaceful,
prosperous reign we've ever known.
一直是每一个和平，
这是我们所知道的最繁荣的统治。
Jon will be warden of the north,
so a good relationship seems likely.
琼恩将成为北境守护，
所以一段良好的关系似乎是可能的。
I don't expect him to spend
much time here going fonnard.
我不指望他花钱
我在这儿呆了很久了。
Well, I suppose that's up to him.
嗯，我想这取决于他。
Sansa, look at me.
珊莎，看着我。
With Jon in the capital,
you'll be the true power in the north.
琼恩在首都
你将成为北境真正的力量。
I'd feel much better about the future
if I left here today
我对未来的感觉会好很多
如果我今天离开这里
believing that you and Daenerys
were allies.
相信你和丹妮莉丝
是盟友。
What are you worried about?
Jon's taking our army with him.
你在担心什么？
琼恩带着我们的军队一起走。
- Your queen still has her dragons...
- She's your queen, too.
-你的女王还有她的龙…
-她也是你的女王
You don't have to be her friend.
你没必要做她的朋友。
But why provoke her?
但是为什么要激怒她呢？
How is that in the best interest
of your family,
这怎么可能是最佳利益呢
你的家人，
- or the north, or...?
- You're afraid of her.
-还是北方，还是…？
-你怕她。
Every good ruler
needs to inspire a bit of fear.
每一个好的统治者
需要激发一点恐惧。
I don't want Jon to go down there.
我不想让乔恩去那里。
The men in my family
don't do well in the capital.
我家里的男人
不要在首都做得很好。
No, but as your brother once told me,
he's not a stark.
不，但正如你哥哥曾经告诉我的，
他不是史塔克家的人。
Are you all right?
你还好吗？
Her people love her, you've seen that.
她的人民爱她，你也看到了。
You've seen how they fight for her.
你也看到他们是怎么为她而战的。
She wants to make the world
a better place.
她想创造世界
一个更好的地方。
I believe in her.
我相信她。
Tyrion.
泰瑞欧。
What if there's someone else?
如果有别人呢？
Someone better?
人更好?
You're not gonna
ride the dragon south?
你不会
骑龙南下？
Jon: Just a horse.
乔恩：只是一匹马。
Rhaegal needs to heal.
雷加尔需要疗伤。
He doesn't need me weighing him down.
他不需要我拖累他。
You weigh as much
as two eras fucking.
你的体重
就像两个时代一样。
I'm taking the free folk home.
我要把自由人带回家。
We've had enough of the south.
我们受够了南方。
The women down here don't like me.
这里的女人不喜欢我。
This is the north, you know.
你知道，这是北方。
And the free folk are welcome to stay.
我们欢迎自由民们留下来。
It isn't home.
这里不是家。
We need room to wander.
我们需要漫游的空间。
I'll take them back
through castle black
我把它们拿回去
穿过黑城堡
as soon as the winter storms pass.
只要冬天的风暴过去。
Back where we belong.
回到属于我们的地方。
It's where he belongs, too.
他也属于这里。
A dire wolf has no place in the south.
可怕的狼在南方没有立足之地。
Will you take him with you?
你会带他一起去吗？
He'll be happier up there.
他在那里会更快乐。
So would you.
你也会的。
I wish I was going with you.
真希望我能和你一起去。
This is farewell, then.
那么，这就是告别了。
You never know.
谁知道呢。
You've got the north in you.
你身上有北方的气息。
The real north.
真正的北方。
Yes, we”, um,
the nights have been getting longer
是的，我们……
夜晚越来越长了
and there wasn't that much
to do in oldtown.
其实并没有那么多
在老城区做的事。
There's only so many books
a person can read, so we...
只有这么多书
一个人可以阅读，所以我们…
I'm sure he knows how it happens, Sam.
我相信他知道这是怎么回事，萨姆。
If it's a boy,
we want to name him "Jon."
如果是个男孩，
我们想给他起名叫“乔恩”。
I hope it's a girl.
我希望是个女孩。
You're the best friend I ever had.
你是我最好的朋友。
You too, Sam.
你也是，萨姆。
Tyrion: Think of the past 20 years.
提利昂：想想过去的20年。
The war, the murder, the misery.
战争，谋杀，苦难。
All of it because Robert Baratheon
loved someone
都是因为劳勃·拜拉席恩
爱的人
who didn't love him back.
没有爱他的人。
How many others know?
还有多少人知道？
Including us? Eight.
包括我们?八个。
Well, then it's not a secret anymore.
那就不再是秘密了。
It's information.
它的信息。
If a handful of people know now,
hundreds will know soon.
如果现在有一小部分人知道了，
数百人很快就会知道。
Then what happens?
然后会发生什么？
She loses the north.
她失去了北方。
She loses the vale,
sansa will make sure of that.
她失去了价值，
珊莎会确保这一点。
No, it's worse than that.
不，比那还糟。
He has the better claim to the throne.
他更有资格继承王位。
He doesn't want the throne.
他不想要王位。
I'm not sure it matters what he wants.
我觉得他想要什么不重要。
The fact is, people are drawn to him.
事实是，人们都被他吸引了。
Wildlings, northmen.
野人,北方人。
He's a war hero.
他是个战争英雄。
He loves our queen.
他爱我们的女王。
And she loves him.
她爱他。
If we marry them,
they could rule together.
如果我们和他们结婚，
他们可以一起统治。
She's his aunt.
她是他的姨妈。
That never stopped a Targaryen before.
坦格利安家族的人从来没被这招吓过。
No, but Jon grew up in winterfell.
没有，但琼恩是在临冬城长大的。
Is marrying your aunt
common in the north?
就是娶你的姨妈
在北方很常见吗？
You know our queen better than I do.
你比我更了解我们的女王。
Do you think
she wants to share the throne?
你认为
她想分享王位？
She does not like to have
her authority questioned.
她不喜欢有
她的权威受到质疑。
Something she has in common
with every monarch who ever lived.
她有一些共同点
和每一位君主在一起。
I worry about her state of mind.
我担心她的精神状态。
We are advisors to the queen.
我们是女王的顾问。
Worrying about her state of mind
is ourjob.
担心她的精神状态
ourjob。
We still have to take king's landing.
我们还得拿下君临。
Maybe Cersei will win and kill us all.
也许瑟曦会赢，把我们都杀了。
That would solve our problems.
这样我们的问题就解决了。
Get to the skiff. Now!
到小船那里去。现在!
Soldier 1: Spears!
士兵1：长矛！
Soldier 2: They're coming round again!
士兵2：他们又回来了！
Soldier 3: Go!
士兵3：快走！
Soldier 4: Clear!
士兵4：安全！
Woman: No!
女人:不!
Soldier 4: Go! Soldier 5: Clear!
士兵4：快走！士兵5：安全！
Missandei?
Missandei吗?
Missandei!
Missandei !
Cersei: Our message
was well-received, then?
瑟曦：我们的信息
很受欢迎吧？
Qyburn: Your people have heard
the usurper is coming.
你的人听说了
篡位者来了。
They are grateful for your protection
within the walls of the red keep.
他们感激你的保护
在红堡的城墙内。
You're certain about the dragon?
你确定是龙吗？
I saw it sink beneath the waves.
我看见它沉到海浪下面。
That must have been glorious.
那一定很光荣。
The glory is yours, my queen.
荣耀属于你，我的女王。
When the war is won,
the lion shall rule the land,
当战争胜利时
狮子将统治大地，
the kraken shall rule the sea...
海怪将统治大海……
And our child
shall one day rule them all.
还有我们的孩子
总有一天会统治他们。
She's coming for you.
她来找你了。
Of course she is.
她当然是。
Keep the gates open.
保持大门敞开。
If she wants to take the castle,
she'll have to murder
如果她想拿下城堡，
她将不得不杀人
thousands of innocent people first.
首先是成千上万无辜的人。
So much for the "breaker of chains."
这就是所谓的“打破锁链的人”。
Grey worm: We will storm the city,
my queen.
灰虫：我们将突袭这座城市，
我的女王。
We will kill your enemies.
All of them.
我们会杀死你的敌人。
所有的。
Varys: Your grace.
瓦里斯：陛下。
I promised you I would look you
in the eye and speak directly
我答应过你我会看你的
直视眼睛，直接说话
if I ever thought
you were making a mistake.
如果我曾经想过
你犯了一个错误。
This is a mistake.
这是一个错误。
You saw my child fall from the sky.
你看到我的孩子从天上掉下来。
They took missandei.
他们带走了弥桑黛。
Varys: Cersei needs to be destroyed,
瓦里斯：瑟曦必须被消灭，
but if we attack king's landing
with drogon and the unsullied
但如果我们进攻君临
有恶龙和无垢者
and the Dothraki, tens of thousands
of innocents will die.
多斯拉克人则有数以万计
无数无辜的人将死去。
That is why Cersei
is bringing them into the red keep.
这就是为什么瑟曦
把他们带进红堡。
These are the people
you came here to protect.
这些人
你是来保护我的。
I beg you, your grace.
我求您了，陛下。
Do not destroy the city
you came to save.
不毁灭这城吗
你是来救人的。
Do not become what you
have always struggled to defeat.
不变成什么你
总是挣扎着去打败。
Do you believe we're here
for a reason, lord varys?
你相信我们在这里吗
有什么原因吗，瓦里斯大人？
I'm here to free the world
from tyrants.
我是来解放世界的
从暴君。
That is my destiny...
这就是我的命运……
And I will serve it,
no matter the cost.
我要端上来，
不计代价。
It could be a fortnight
before Jon and the allied armies
可能是两周
在琼恩和联军之前
make it to king's landing.
去君临吧。
In the meantime,
demand Cersei's surrender.
与此同时，
要求瑟曦投降。
Offer her her life
in exchange for the throne.
给她生命
以换取王位。
If there's a chance
to avoid the coming slaughter,
如果有机会的话
为了避免即将到来的屠杀，
we should make the effort.
我们应该努力。
Speaking to Cersei
will not prevent a slaughter.
对瑟曦说
不会阻止一场屠杀。
But perhaps it's good the people see
但也许让人们看到是好事
that Daenerys stormborn made
every effort to avoid bloodshed,
是风暴降生丹妮莉丝做的
一切避免流血的努力，
and Cersei Lannister refused.
瑟曦·兰尼斯特拒绝了。
They should know whom to blame
when the sky falls down upon them.
他们应该知道该怪谁
天塌下来的时候。
I've served tyrants most of my life.
我大半辈子都在为暴君服务。
They all talk about destiny.
他们都在谈论命运。
She's a girl who walked into a fire
with three stones
她是一个走进火里的女孩
用三块石头
and walked out with three dragons.
带着三条龙走了出去。
How could she not believe in destiny?
她怎么能不相信命运呢？
Perhaps that's the problem.
也许这就是问题所在。
Her life has convinced her that
she was sent here to save us all.
她的生活使她确信
她被派来拯救我们所有人。
And how do you know she wasn't?
你怎么知道她不是？
Then there's the problem of Jon snow.
接下来就是琼恩·雪诺的问题。
Perhaps it's actually a solution.
也许这实际上是一个解决方案。
You know them both.
他们两个你都认识。
Tell me, who do you think
would make a better ruler?
告诉我，你认为是谁
会成为更好的统治者吗？
He doesn't want the throne.
他不想要王位。
That's why he bent the knee.
这就是他屈膝的原因。
Have you considered the best ruler
你考虑过最好的尺子吗
might be someone
who doesn't want to rule?
可能是某人
谁不想统治呢？
We're discussing treason.
我们在讨论叛国罪。
Don't pretend
you haven't thought about it.
不要假装
你还没想过呢。
Of course I've thought about it.
Thoughts aren't treason.
我当然想过了。
思想不是叛国。
He's temperate and measured.
他有节制，有分寸。
He's a man, which makes him more
appealing to the lords of Westeros,
他是个男人，所以他更
向维斯特洛的领主们求助
whose support we are going to need.
我们需要他的支持。
Joffrey was a man.
乔佛里是个男人。
I don't think a cock
is a true qualification,
我不认为是鸡巴
是一个真正的资格，
as I'm sure you'd agree.
我相信你也会同意
And he's the heir to the throne.
他是王位的继承人。
Yes, because he's a man.
Cocks are important, I'm afraid.
是的，因为他是个男人。
恐怕鸡巴很重要。
What about my earlier proposal?
我之前的提议怎么样？
They could rule together
as king and queen.
他们可以一起统治
作为国王和王后。
She's too strong for him.
她对他来说太强大了。
She'd bend him to her will,
as she already has.
她会让他屈从于她的意志
她已经这么做了。
He could temper her worst impulses.
他能缓和她最坏的冲动。
As you have?
像你一样？
You're drinking quite a lot.
你喝得太多了。
A Targaryen father and a stark mother.
坦格利安家族的父亲和史塔克家族的母亲。
Jon's the one man alive
琼恩是唯一活着的人
who might actually be able to keep
the north in the seven kingdoms.
谁可能会保留
北方的七国。
How many kings and queens
have you served?
有多少国王和王后
你服过役吗？
Five? Six? I've lost count.
五个?六个?我数不清了。
- You've always known my reasons.
- At a certain point,
-你一直都知道我的理由。
-在某一时刻
you choose a person you believe in,
and you fight for that person.
你选择一个你信任的人，
你为那个人而奋斗。
Even if you know it's a mistake?
即使你知道这是个错误？
I believe in our queen.
我相信我们的女王。
She'll make the right choice.
她会做出正确的选择。
With the help of her onal advisors.
在她个人顾问的帮助下。
You know where my onalty stands.
你知道我的立场。
You know I will never
betray the realm.
你知道我永远不会
背叛王国。
What is the realm?
什么是王国？
A vast continent,
home to millions of people,
广袤的大陆，
这里是数百万人的家园
most of whom don't care
who sits on the iron throne.
大多数人都不在乎
谁坐在铁王座上。
Millions of people,
many of whom will die
数百万人，
他们中的许多人会死去
if the wrong person
sits on that throne.
如果找错了人
坐在那个宝座上。
We don't know their names,
but they're just as real as you and I.
我们不知道他们的名字，
但他们和你我一样真实
They deserve to live.
他们应该活下去。
They deserve food for their children.
他们应该为自己的孩子提供食物。
I will act in their interest,
no matter the personal cost.
我会为他们的利益行事
不管付出多少个人代价。
So, what happens to her?
那么，她后来怎么样了？
Please.
请。
I've spoken as honestly as I can.
我已经尽可能诚实地说了。
Each of us has a choice to make.
我们每个人都要做出选择。
I pray we choose wisely.
我祈祷我们能做出明智的选择。
Man 1: All right,
I'll put another one on it.
男1：好吧，
我再放一个上去。
Man 2: He's headed down to the cellar.
男人2：他去地窖了。
Man 3: I'll need a cart over here.
Man 4: That's it, thanks.
男士3：我需要一辆手推车。
男4：就这样，谢谢。
Thank you.
谢谢你！
As are the rest of her advisors.
她的其他顾问也是。
What happened?
发生了什么事?
Euron greyjoy ambushed
queen Daenerys and her eret.
攸伦·葛雷乔伊中了埋伏
丹妮莉丝王后和她的女儿。
One of the dragons was killed,
several ships destroyed,
其中一条龙被杀了
几艘船被毁，
missandei captured.
missandei被俘。
I always wanted to be there
when they execute your sister.
我一直想去那里
当他们处决你妹妹的时候。
Seems like I won't get the chance.
看来我没有机会了。
They're going to destroy that city.
他们要摧毁那座城市。
You know they will.
你知道他们会的。
Jaime: Have you ever
run away from a fight?
詹姆：你有没有
从一场打斗中逃跑？
You're not like your sister.
You're not.
你不像你姐姐。
你不是。
You're better than she is.
你比她强。
You're a good man
and you can't save her.
你是个好人
你救不了她。
You don't need to die with her.
你不需要和她一起死。
Stay here.
待在这里。
Stay with me.
别离开我。
Please.
请。
Stay.
留下来。
You think I'm a good man?
你觉得我是个好人？
I pushed a boy out a tower window,
crippled him for life
我把一个男孩推出了塔楼的窗户，
使他终生残疾
for Cersei.
瑟曦。
I strangled my cousin
with my own hands
我勒死了我的表弟
用我自己的双手
just to get back to Cersei.
就为了回到瑟曦身边
I would have murdered
我会杀了你
every man, woman and child in riverrun
奔流城的每一个男人、女人和孩子
for Cersei.
瑟曦。
She's hateful.
她是可恨的。
And so am I.
我也是。
My lord.
我的主。
Queen Daenerys demands
Cersei's unconditional surrender
丹妮莉丝王后要求
瑟曦无条件投降
and the immediate release
of missandei of naath.
立即释放
乃特的弥珊黛。
Queen Cersei demands
Daenerys's unconditional surrender.
瑟曦太后要求
丹妮莉丝无条件投降。
If she refuses, missandei of naath
will die here and now.
如果她拒绝，纳斯的弥桑黛
会死在此时此地。
Beurn...
Beurn……
You're a rational man.
你是个理性的人。
Or so I flatter myself, my lord.
至少我是这么想的，大人。
We have a chance here,
我们还有机会
perhaps our last chance,
to avoid carnage.
也许是我们最后的机会，
为了避免大屠杀。
Yes.
是。
Help me.
帮助我。
I don't want to see this city burn.
我不想看到这座城市被烧毁。
I don't want to hear the screams
of children burning alive.
我不想听到尖叫声
孩子们被活活烧死。
No, it is not a pleasant sound.
不，这不是悦耳的声音。
I... I don't want to hear it.
我…我不想听。
Help me save this city.
帮我拯救这座城市。
My lord, I am only a mouthpiece
for our queen.
大人，我只是个喉舌
为了我们的女王。
Tyrion: Your queen.
提利昂：你的女王。
Cersei is queen of the seven kingdoms.
瑟曦是七大王国的女王。
You are her subject.
你是她的主题。
Her reign is over.
她的统治结束了。
You understand this.
Help her understand it.
你懂的。
帮助她理解。
We understand nothing of the sort.
我们对此一无所知。
Your queen's last dragon
is vulnerable.
你王后的最后一条龙
是脆弱的。
Your armies
are battle-weary and depleted,
你的军队
疲于奔命，精疲力竭，
while ours have been reinforced
with the golden compan...
而我们的部队已经增援了
有黄金陪伴……
Captain: Ready!
船长:准备好了!
Nock!
诺!
Draw!
画!
I know you don't care
about your people.
我知道你不在乎
关于你的人。
Why should you?
你为什么要这么做？
They hate you and you hate them.
他们恨你，你也恨他们。
But you're not a monster.
但你不是怪物。
I know this.
我知道这个。
I know this because I've seen it.
我知道这些是因为我亲眼所见。
You've always loved your children.
你一直很爱你的孩子。
More than yourself...
不仅仅是你自己……
More than Jaime...
不只是詹姆……
More than anything.
比什么都重要。
I beg you.
我求你了。
If not for yourself,
then for your child.
如果不是为了你自己，
然后是你的孩子。
Your reign is over,
你的统治结束了
but that doesn't mean
your life has to end.
但这并不意味着
你的生命必须结束。
It doesn't mean your baby has to die.
这并不意味着你的孩子必须死。
If you have any last words,
now is the time.
如果你有什么遗言
现在是时候了。
Dracarys.
Dracarys。
No.
否。